otel.com 2016-04-08

# Site Security & Privacy - Otel.com

Otel.com has the highest security measures as well as being a member of GlobalSign Security System and Authenticated Payment Program which has been developed by Visa-3D Secure otel.com is proud to have applied a system complying with the PCI DSS standards as established by Visa and MasterCard. The PCI DSS lays out a set of comprehensive requirements for enhancing data security of the payment account which otel.com has implemented. 

Otel.com guarantees that the privacy and security of all personal and financial information shared by you, will be protected in compliance with the highest e-commerce security standards when exchanged over the internet. 

The Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology we use ensures the privacy and security of all transactions. SSL technology encrypts data before it is transmitted, so that only the authorized recipient can have access to it. In addition to SSL technology, your information is further protected by the following: segmentation and compartmentalization of information on our network to ensure restricted access to customer information databases; physical and logical barriers to unauthorized access; and a best of breed firewall system. 

## PRIVACY POLICY

### Collection and Use of Information

This site requires that customers share personal and/or financial information to in order to receive the services offered. With the following exceptions, such information will be used strictly for the purposes of providing the services requested:

Telephone numbers may be used to contact customers in case of an urgent need relating to an existing reservation or request for services.

E-mail addresses may be used to inform clients of services and offers which are most likely to be of interest to them. With respect to this use of personal information, customers may at any time indicate their preference not to receive such information by changing their account settings. Or may click on a link named “Unsubscribe” which is embedded with every email sent by otel.com in order not to receive future messages.

### Retention of Personal Data

Legal obligations may require that otel.com retain personal information for a specified period of time. If so, otel.com will only retain personal information for the duration of the specified period. Generic demographic data gleaned from personal information and used for marketing purposes may be retained longer but will be purged of any information which can be used identify customers personally.

### Information Shared With Third Parties

Otel.com will share your personal information with banks, processing companies, and service providers involved in providing you the services requested. Unless there is an emergency and otel.com is legally obliged to do so by law, otel.com will never share your personal information with any other third parties.

### Visitor IP Logging

Otel.com logs visitor IP addresses to optimize server performance and to track visitor movement through our site. In the case of the latter, the information is used by our web analytics software to provide us with important marketing information about our customers.

### Cookies

Upon your initial visit to our site, otel.com will automatically set a cookie -a small piece of data- on your hard drive to welcome you back to the site upon subsequent visits and to save your chosen site parameters. We do not use cookies to collect any information other than just described, and the information stored in a cookie can in no way be used to identify you personally. You can always avoid receiving cookies by setting your Web browser to refuse them.

### Links to Third Party Sites

This website contains links to third-party websites. otel.com's Privacy Policy does not apply to these sites, and otel.com makes no guarantees as to the privacy policy of any third party sites to which it contains links.

### Changes in Privacy Policy

Otel.com may change its Privacy Policy at any time without notice. You agree that any information shared by you in relation to a booking is subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your most recent booking. If you have any questions or concerns regarding any provision of this policy, you are urged to contact us.

### Company Information

Prodo Travel

Mehmet Akif Cad. No : 60 K/2 Koskluciftlik Nicosia - Cyprus

+(90) 212 315 14 91
